[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "Where are you going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "I'm interested in what happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "What the hell are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "It's an interview people are still talking about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Why do you have such conflict with them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "I don't think I really do have any conflict with them in the sense that -- that that guy you're talking about, that photographer, I mean, I think the most important thing to remember is I did not punch the guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "I would call them a tax, it's a tax on show business, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "You have a very different opinion than I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "If I could press a button tomorrow and flush them all down some swirling sewer vortex, I would do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "But you can never have any more publicity in any newspaper or magazine for anything you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, that's not really practical.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Any names?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Russell Crowe"]}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "But who are the ones you look at and go, that's where I want to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "VB", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, Russell Crowe is extremely prepared.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", ":", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "When you wanted to get into show business, was part of the allure of it being famous, if you're honest, when you look back to that time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I'd have to say -- and this is true of a lot of comedians, and I've talked to other comedians and heard them say the same thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "If you were running a news network, what would you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Well, first let me just back up a little bit and say, I don't have to live in the real world, I'm a fiction writer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Well, you know the answer to that, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Go on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Never?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "A bit awkward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Who is the biggest most romantic sexual singer you've ever deployed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJS", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Holy cow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Has to be, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Has to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Were you really trying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "You know what, I always like to make the guest feel like they're the star.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "You know, contrary to public perception.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "You've already sold, what, 10 million albums?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "WP", ",", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Something like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "What's the worst song you've ever written?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "I don't even want to say it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", ":", "IN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "How?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "And I -- because -- well, I can explain all that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Literally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Literally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "What is the song of all the songs that you've ever been involved with -- what is the one, if I said, right, Glen, you've got five minute to live, you can play one song to be remembered by, the defining song?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Well, you know, I have my favorite records.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Glen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "``", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 297, "question": "What's your -- what's your number one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "I loved \"One of These Nights.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Adele"]}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "And who of all the acts out there now, who's the one that excites you, the modern crowd?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "RB", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Well, you know, I love Adele.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Can I touch it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Yes, go ahead.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "How does it feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "ATSON: It feels nice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "How does it really feel to be Bubba Watson right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "It's overwhelming.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bubba Watson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "That is genuinely why, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "How do you feel now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Well, I don't put myself in those situations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "When was the last time you hit a man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Good shot?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "You're in the zone and you're winning, what do you experience?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Well, when you're out there, you have to take the winning -- winner's attitude, as I do, and I can't go out there thinking I'm feeling sorry because they're trying to win, too.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Not just any old champion, to be a great champion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Well, it's just hard work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Is it all of it, Usain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "It's everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "If you want to show me the door, that's fine, too.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Do you remember the night that she died well, or is it now something you've blocked out of your head?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "No, I remember it quite well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Where are you going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "I'm interested in what happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "What the hell are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Let me help you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Now you want to know what happened that night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "-- on your story.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "I'm curious about --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Am I right so far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "So far.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "No, but your questions are boring, because -- I mean, even what you just said, are you sure the people at Tibet give a (EXPLETIVE DELETED) about any of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "I think you're here because you've written a book about your life.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tibet"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Than the murder of your wife?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "I didn't murder my wife.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Maria"]}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Do you think there is a good chance you can get back together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "I cannot speak for Maria.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Was it more that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "I would say that it makes no difference.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "How are you handling it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "The big white elephant in the room we can't avoid.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "Did you ever touch a beaver?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "Well, it's all of the above and a whole lot more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Would she have ever gone down that route, do you think, without Bobby Brown in her life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Well, if not him, somebody else.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bobby Brown"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Do you think she had that tendency anyway?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "I think that we all as artists, because we're highly sensitive people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tyler"]}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "I know everything, Tyler.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Because you supplied the plane, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "Amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "What was the secret ingredient that he had?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "He was a great generalist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "Have you read \"Fifty Shades of Grey\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "I read the first seven chapters.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Was there anything in there you hadn't already done yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "EX", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "I know you probably imagined differently and have several nights during the week when you go to bed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 738, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 739, "answer": "You surprise me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "No manacles?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "Did you read the entire trilogy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "It's unreadable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 756, "question": "Why would you read that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 757, "answer": "Just out of pure curiosity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 779, "question": "You didn't tell me then, though, did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 780, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 792, "question": "How much weight have you lost?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 793, "answer": "Not much at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 807, "question": "Hollywood smiley?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 808, "answer": "I got some free -- those things in a luxury lounge once, those -- I thought those made me gag.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 819, "question": "What made you go on this vanity kick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 820, "answer": "It wasn't a vanity kick.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "``", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", ":", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 844, "question": "Where would you be without that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 845, "answer": "-- \"The death of a fight-useless chubby loser with -- who never cleans his teeth and stinks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 849, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 850, "answer": "Cut that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]